We came home after finishing our Friday morning workout and
two of our pets were
waiting for us. One or two of them, Lupi,
came and rested for a while
because everything was
going well at night. But Lupi never came and
stayed there
. She was always playing with the baby. As soon as we left, she started to get really hungry.  If you see me as soon as I arrive,
I'll definitely grab a green tea for refreshment.
Lipton's green tea comes in many flavors
.  So I'll come back once a week and
pick up each flavor.   If you
come to Lipton Green Tea and see that it has
zero sugar and zero calories, then when we get
cravings, we eat something else,
and then the workout we do is
useless.
This is an alternative to that, and I
think it's the best option.  It
contains catechins, which
boosts metabolism.  You just need to sit back, relax for 10 to 15
minutes, have a sip, and
then
start your day's routine again.
Anyway, it's
after 12:30 before I have to leave for the office.  There will
be a lot of waiting work on the way.  I have
to finish all that and then go.  So I freshened up,
went to my mother's house, and
left for the office.  If you
want details about this product, I've
pinned it in the comments, so check it out and
buy it.
You can also purchase the product on Amazon Bling
.